[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In which film did the main character have to get rid of his vices such as smoking, drinking, gambling in order to inherit a large sum of cash?", "correct_answer": "Easy Money", "incorrect_answers": ["Brewsters Millions", "Heaven Can Wait", "Arthur 2-On the Rocks"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What 1991 movie was the winner of the Academy Award for Best Picture at the 64th Academy Awards in 1992?", "correct_answer": "The Silence of the Lambs", "incorrect_answers": ["The Prince of Tides", "Beauty and the Beast", "JFK"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The constant e is present in countless fields of mathematics but its most significant function is related to its use in what?", "correct_answer": "The base of natural logarithms", "incorrect_answers": ["The characteristics of unitary matrices", "The mantissa of common logarithms", "The limiting value of the sum of the squares of the odd numbers"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these statements is true about carnivorous organisms in general?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["They feed on vertebrate animals.", "They feed through scavenging.", "They feed on invertebrate animals."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Oklahoma has more man-made lakes than any other state.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Kelly Bishop, who plays Marjorie Houseman (Babys mom) in the movie Dirty Dancing, also played the mother on this TV show.", "correct_answer": "Gilmore Girls", "incorrect_answers": ["The O.C.", "One Tree Hill", "Malcolm in the Middle"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie, Casablanca, who is the ma\u00eetre dh\u00f4tel of Ricks Caf\u00e9 Americain?", "correct_answer": "Carl", "incorrect_answers": ["Ferrari", "Sascha", "Abdul"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The movie Back to the Future, directed by Robert Zemeckis, was released in what year?", "correct_answer": "1985", "incorrect_answers": ["1955", "1986", "1987"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This dish is prepared in Norway.  Its name means cod soaked in plutonium.  It is dried whitefish soaked in lye, a strong solution of sodium or potassium hydroxide.", "correct_answer": "Lutefisk", "incorrect_answers": ["Limburger", "Criadillas", "Yule brod"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The name of this volcano, located on the Alaska Peninsula, means new eruption.", "correct_answer": "Novarupta", "incorrect_answers": ["Newatsa", "Mount Rainier", "Mount Hood"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these three sets is the largest: the set of all whole numbers, the set of all even numbers, the set of  all odd numbers?", "correct_answer": "They are the same size", "incorrect_answers": ["The set of all even numbers", "The set of all whole numbers", "The set of all odd numbers"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Do Lacoste have shoes as part of their collections?", "correct_answer": "Yes", "incorrect_answers": ["No"]}]